travelagentcentral.com 2017-12-10

# Privacy Policy | Questex

### Privacy Policy

The following Privacy Statement summarizes the various ways that Questex LLC (“Questex”) treats the information you provide while using www.questex.com or any other Questex site. It is our goal to bring you information that is tailored to your individual needs and, at the same time, protect your privacy. This Privacy Statement does not cover information collected elsewhere, including offline and on sites linked to or from any of our sites.

Please read this Privacy Statement carefully. Your use of, accessing, and/or registration on any aspect of our sites will constitute your agreement to this Privacy Statement. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not use our sites. If you have any questions regarding our privacy statement, please feel free to contact us by e-mail at [privacy@questex.com](mailto:privacy@questex.com).

In addition to reviewing this Privacy Policy, please read our Terms of Use. Your use of the our sites constitutes agreement to its terms and conditions as well.

This Privacy Statement may be modified from time to time; the date of the most recent revisions will appear on this page, so check back often. Any change, update or modification we make will be effective immediately upon posting on our site(s). If we are going to be using the information collected from users in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection, we will send affected users written notice of the change by e-mail. Continued access of our sites by you will constitute your acceptance of any changes or revisions to the Privacy Statement.

**Information Collected by Questex**  
In general, you may visit our sites without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information.

As you browse our sites, we collect log file, IP address of your computer, and other standard tracking data we use to evaluate site traffic and usage patterns. Such information is aggregated with tracking data from all site visitors. We will use the information to personalize our sites according to your preferences based on the aggregated information. We also use the aggregated information to evaluate products and services we may offer to you.

Portions of our sites may require you to give us personally identifiable information, such as your name, job title, company, physical mailing address, e-mail address, telephone and fax numbers and, if applicable, financial information such as your credit card information, for, among other purposes:

(i) registration for attendance at certain Questex trade shows, conferences and events;  
(ii) subscriptions to our publications, including e-newsletters; and  
(iii) to access certain features or functions of our websites.

If you communicate with us by e-mail, post messages to any of our chat groups, bulletin boards or forums, or otherwise complete online forms, surveys or contest entries, any information provided in such communications may be collected as personal information. You always have the option not to provide the information we request. If you choose not to provide the information we request, you can still visit most of our sites, but you may be unable to access certain options and services.

**How We Use Your Information**  
If you elect to provide us personal information, we may use it to:

(i) deliver the service you requested;  
(ii) in connection with your registration for a trade show, conference or event;  
(iii) in connection with your subscription to our publications;  
(iv) to respond to your inquiries and contact you about our Site and/or Services;  
(v)for any other purpose disclosed at the time the information is collected or to which you consent.

If you submit financial information, we use that information primarily to verify your credit and collect payments for your purchases, orders, registrations, etc.

**Personal Information Sharing**  
We may share your personal information with our affiliates and with our partners, including our exhibitors, sponsors and advertisers, for marketing, advertising, and/or product/service offering purposes, and with others who are licensed to access your personal information by any of the foregoing. Also, we rent e-mail lists compiled from e-mail addresses gathered from our sites. While we will seek to require all such third parties to follow appropriate privacy policies and will not authorize them to use this information except for the express purpose for which it is provided, Questex does not bear any responsibility for any actions or policies of third parties.

If you do not wish to have your personally identifying information shared, or if you do not wish to receive future commercial communications from us by e-mail, you may unsubscribe or opt-out, as described below – see “Opt-Out Option.”

We may also allow access to your information by third parties that provide us with services, such as development services, but only for the purpose of and to the extent necessary to provide those services and only if those third parties take appropriate precautions to safeguard your information.

In addition, we reserve the right to use the information we collect about you and/or your computer, which may at times be able to identify you, for any lawful business purpose, including to help diagnose problems with our servers, to gather broad demographic information, and to otherwise administer our sites, or if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Questex or to protect and defend the rights or property of Questex, or to enforce our terms of service.

In addition, as our business changes, we may buy or sell various assets. In the event all or a portion of the assets owned or controlled by Questex, or any subsidiary or affiliated entity, are sold, assigned, transferred or acquired by another company, the information from and about our sites’ users may be among the transferred assets.

**Special Notification for California Residents**  
If you reside in California and you have provided us with personal information, you may request information about our disclosures of certain categories of your personal information (if any) to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. Such requests must be submitted to us at [privacy@questex.com](mailto:privacy@questex.com). Within thirty days of receiving such a request, we will provide a list of the categories of personal information disclosed to third parties (if any) for third-party direct marketing purposes during the immediately preceding calendar year, along with the names and addresses of these third parties. This request may be made no more than once per calendar year. We reserve our right not to respond to requests submitted other than to the email address specified in this paragraph.

**Aggregated Anonymous Information**  
We reserve the right to use, transfer, sell, and share aggregated, anonymous data about our users as a group for any business purpose, such as analyzing usage trends, improving our products and/or services, and seeking compatible advertisers and partners.We reserve the right to use, transfer, sell, and share aggregated, anonymous data about our users as a group for any business purpose, such as analyzing usage trends, improving our products and/or services, and seeking compatible advertisers and partners.

**Information on Children**  
As a business-to-business company, we have created and maintain sites that are not intended for use by children, particularly those under age 13, and we do not knowingly collect information from children. On-line registration and website usage is restricted to adults who are professionally engaged in the businesses we serve. No one under age 13 is allowed to provide any personal information or use any public discussion areas, forums and chats comprising part of our sites. Minors between the ages of 13 and 17 must get the permission of their parent(s) or legal guardian(s) before making purchases, including subscriptions, on our sites. In the event that we learn we have collected any personal information from a child under the age of 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information from our database as quickly as possible

**Removing or Correcting Your Information**  
Many of our Site functions (but not all) provide you with the option of correcting, updating and modifying your personal and/or financial information, or visitor profile, at any time and as often as desired. The only item of information you cannot change is your username ID selected at registration for a trade show, event or conference.

If you would like to update, remove or correct your information and are unable to do so through your user profile, please contact [privacy@questex.com](mailto:privacy@questex.com).

**Opt-Out Option**  
Visitors to our sites and users of our services can decide if they want to receive targeted promotional information from Questex or targeted promotional information sponsored by our marketing partners. On the visitor registration pages, you can state preferences regarding advertising and promotional communications from Questex or our partners. Should visitors accept promotional email from Questex, any email they receive will include instructions on how to be removed from our promotional email list.

If you do not wish to have your personally identifying information shared, or if you do not wish to receive future commercial communications from us by e-mail, you may change your preferences at any time simply by: (i) writing to us (and please include your e-mail address), or (ii) by following the unsubscribe instructions contained within the e-mail you receive from us. We will update your preferences as soon as is reasonably practicable. If you have registered on any part of our sites, please use the mechanism on our sites that allows you to change or update your profile, preferences or information, if available, to keep all such data accurate and up-to-date. The only item of information you cannot change is your username ID selected at registration for a trade show, event or conference.

Please note that if you opt-out as described above, we will not be able to remove your personal information from the databases of third parties with which we have already shared your personal information (i.e., to which we have provided your personal information prior to our receipt of your opt-out request).

To opt out of communications from these third parties, please contact the third party sender. Questex does not bear any responsibility for ensuring that any third party complies with your opt-out or unsubscribe request vis-à-vis its own lists.

**Third Party and Affiliated Links**  
Our sites may from time to time contain external links to other websites, including suppliers, advertisers and affiliates. We have no control over, and are not responsible for, the content of, or information gathered by, these other websites. We do not endorse any of these websites or the products or services associated with such websites merely because they are linked to any of our sites. In addition, users of our sites should also be aware that, when you voluntarily disclose personal information in chat areas or bulletin boards, that information may be collected by others and may result in unsolicited messages from others.

**Cookies**  
A “cookie” is a bit of data sent by a website through the browser to the computer of the user visiting the site, and enables our sites to return the results the browser expects. We may use temporary, session-specific cookies to ensure visits to our sites is smooth and customized for the visitor – for example, to control the display of ads, to track usage patterns on our sites, to deliver editorial content, and to record registration and personalization information. Such cookies allow us to provide a visitor’s browser with information tailored to the visitor’s preferences and needs. We also may use permanent or persistent cookies that remain on a visitor’s computer after the visitor leaves our sites. We use this data on an anonymous basis and we do not correlate this information with personal data of any user.

Most website browsers automatically accept cookies, but you may be able to turn off the cookie acceptance option in your browser’s settings. However, disabling the cookie support function of the browser may prevent some portions of our sites from functioning properly, and you may not be able to utilize fully all of our sites’ features and information. We may from time to time use advertising companies to develop banner ads for our sites. These ads may contain cookies that may be sent to your browser through the banner ads. We do not have control over cookies placed by our advertisers, nor do we have access to any information their cookies may collect.

We might also receive information about you from third parties that track your activities on the web or from partners or third party service providers with whom you’ve transacted business. These third parties generally would be other providers that you have authorized to obtain and share information about you and/or information about your activities on the internet, such as sites you visit using your computer or mobile device. We may combine this information with other information we have collected from you by other means and we may use and/or disclose that combined information consistent with this Policy.

**Use of Google Analytics Tools for Display Advertising**  
We may employ tools provided by Google Analytics to support Display Advertising, including Remarketing, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, the DoubleClick Campaign Manager integration and/or Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting.

In general, this means that:

(i) Third-party vendors, including Google, may show our ads on sites across the Internet (including non-Questex sites) based upon your visits to this site.  
(ii) You may receive interest-based advertising on our site based on the types of sites visited from your device or other anonymous data Google has collected.  
(iii) To implement these tools, we and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third- party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on past visits to our website and to report how ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to our site.  
(iv) We use data from Google’s Interest-based advertising or 3rd-party audience data (such as age, gender, and interests) to better serve you, including to improve our site, products, and services and to provide you with access to content that we believe will be of interest to you.  
To opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising, please use the opt-out feature in Google’s Ad Settings at www.google.com/settings/ads/. Visitors may also use the Google Analytics opt-out Browser add on (available for download here https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/) to opt out of these advertisements online.

We may also use one or more of the following features of Google AdWords Interest-Based Advertising features: remarketing; interest categories; similar audiences; demographic and location targeting. We follow Google’s policy for advertising based on interest and location, which you can view here: https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/143465.

We will not combine any analytic data collected through these services with your personally indefinable information without first receiving your explicit consent.

**Security and Encryption**  
We use procedural and technical safeguards to protect your personal information against loss or theft as well as unauthorized access and disclosure to protect your privacy, including encryption, “firewalls” and Secure Socket Layers. We treat data as an asset that must be protected against loss and unauthorized access. We employ many different security techniques to protect such data from unauthorized access by users inside and outside the company.

**Non-US Users**  
This Web site is operated in the United States. If you are located in the European Union or elsewhere outside of the United States, please be aware that any information you provided to us will be transferred to the United States. By using our Web site, participating in any of our services and/or providing us with your information, you consent to this transfer and to our collection and use of your information as set forth above.

**Privacy Statement Coordinator**  
If you have any questions regarding our privacy statement, please feel free to contact us by letter at the address below, or by e-mail at [privacy@questex.com](mailto:privacy@questex.com).

We read every message submitted and try to reply promptly to everyone.

Questex LLC  
275 Grove Street  
Suite 2-130  
Newton, MA 02466
